Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Graphics, 1950-2007, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  - Subseries VII.A. Graphics and Illustrations, 1998-2000, undated; 1.25 linear foot in 1 record carton and 1 flat file folder.
    - John Lindell. "Portholes and Moments 12 (after Tom of Finland)" [Illustrated story. Signed letter from author], 1992; cuid24135 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Julius "Little Dick's Photo Album", Undated; cuid24136 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Lüger. [Two print portfolios of drawings published by Colt Studio], 1992-1993; cuid24137 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous [Pieces on Rex, Harry Bush, and George Quaintance], 1996; cuid24138 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Rip Colt [Untitled drawing by Rip Colt/Jim French], Undated; cuid24139 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Tom of Finland [photocopies of drawings; correspondence], 1991; cuid24140 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Untitled [drawings by unknown artist], Undated; cuid24141 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Subseries VII.B. Japanese Publications, 1950-2007, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
    This subseries contains Japanese gay BDSM (bondage, discipline, dominance and submission, sadomasochism) erotic Manga and magazines. Material is in Japanese.
    The Japanese publications are in alphabetical order by author or artist and alphabetically by publication title within.
    - G-Pro Party. G-Project Co. v.1, Undated; cuid24142 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. "Emono" and other stories, 1998; cuid24143 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. The House of the Brutes v.1, 2007; cuid24144 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. The House of the Brutes v.2, 2007; cuid24145 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. The House of the Brutes v.3, 2007; cuid24146 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. "Jujitsu Kyoshi" and Other Stories, 1994; cuid24147 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Naburi-mono, 1994; cuid24148 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Shirogane-no-Hanna v.1, 2002; cuid24149 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Shirogane-no-Hanna v.2, 2002; cuid24150 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Gengoroh Tagame. Shirogane-no-Hanna v.3, 2002; cuid24151 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Goh Mishima. Otoko - The Man, Undated; cuid24152 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Jinb Gym. "Kaze no yukue" and Other Stories, 2006; cuid24153 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jogg Comics (Raizo Taira). May, 2004; cuid24154 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jogg Comics (Raizo Taira). July, 2004; cuid24155 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kumagoro. Otoko-Dosukoi! v.1, 2001; cuid24156 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kumagoro. Otoko-Dosukoi! v.2, 2002; cuid24157 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Masurao - photographed by Yoshito Kazu. G-Project Co, Undated; cuid24158 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Sabu. March 1979. n.49, cuid24159 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabu. Aug 1982. n.90, cuid24160 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabu. Aug 1985. n.126, cuid24161 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabu. April 1989. n.195, cuid24162 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Nov., 1999; cuid24163 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Feb 2000. n.1, cuid24164 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. April 2000. n.2, cuid24165 (Box 19, Folder 2a)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Aug 2000. n.3, cuid24166 (Box 19, Folder 2a)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. March 2001. n.4, cuid24167 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. June 2003. n.6, cuid24168 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - SM-Z. G-Project. Aug 2004. n.8, cuid24169 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - SM-Z Super. G-Project. Summer 2006. n.7, cuid24170 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - SM-Z Super. G-Project. Autumn 2006. n.8, cuid24171 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - (Unknown) ?For Youngmen & Guys? May 1975. n.28, cuid24172 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - (Unknown) ?Ho-Man? Sept 2004. n.61, cuid24173 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - (Unknown) October, 1950; cuid24174 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - (Unknown) July, 1951; cuid24175 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.; 3 electronic discs (cd-rom)
  The materials are listed in alphabetical order by title, followed by author name and date.
  This series contains erotic stories originally published via websites, online forums, and email chains. Marshall printed the stories out on paper. A majority of the folders contain complete stories, while a few have been only partially printed out. A selection of the stories were printed on the reverse of Richard Marshall's professional correspondence.
  - 2 x 2, Bawdy Pen, 2000; cuid24176 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - A/C Repair, Romaine954, 1998; cuid24177 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Abandoned House Raunch, Bkcycler, 2001; cuid24178 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Accident, Scathole, Undated; cuid24179 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Adonis Brotherhood (Part 3), Master SIR, 2000; cuid24180 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Adult Incest, John Ommestrup, 1996, cuid24181 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Adult Incest: Man to Man, Kennyb, 1996, cuid24182 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Adult Theater Raunch, Jocksniffer, Undated; cuid24183 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Adventures on I-10 (Parts 1-3), Dick Hunter, 2000; cuid24184 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Adventures on the Road (Part 4), Bearbtmboy, 2003; cuid24185 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - After the NCO Club, Happenstance, Undated; cuid24186 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Afternoon Delight, Slick, 1997, cuid24187 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Afterwork (Parts 1- 5), Antoms, 2001, cuid24188 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Agua Por El Papi Cholo, Tommyhawk1, Undated; cuid24189 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Alex and the Hustler, Joe Wilson, Undated; cuid24190 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - All Dad's Fault, Unknown, 2001; cuid24191 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - All In the Family, Maipenraikhap, 1999, cuid24192 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Almost Like A Story, Manx952joy, 2002; cuid24193 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Always: Daddy's Pup, Unknown, Undated; cuid24194 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Another Hardon Family (Part 1): Hotline Report, Marc Tremaine, 1998; cuid24195 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Another One For the Gang, C2cbearhug, 2003, cuid24196 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Another Special For the Trash Shack, Bid Red, Undated; cuid24197 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Another Working Day, Billy Boy, 1999, cuid24198 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Anthony, The Mover, Unknown, Undated; cuid24199 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Arab Dirt: Dirt Pig Does a Middle Eastern Businessman, Dirt Pig, Undated; cuid24200 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Arabian Adventure, Sam4U, Undated; cuid24201 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Arcade Adventures # 2, Gloryhole Lover, 2000, cuid24202 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Armpit Fantasy Comes to Life, sweaty20, 1998; cuid24203 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Armpit Slave, Sweaty, Undated; cuid24204 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Army Grunt, Jon H, 2001, cuid24205 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - The Army: Code Yellow/Code Brown, Bkcycler, 2002; cuid24206 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Army Property, Shulabin, 2002; cuid24207 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Arrogance (Parts 1-4), Roderick Shafton, 2000; cuid24208 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Art Class, Ozzie Red, 2002, cuid24209 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Assistant Jock Sniffer, Ted Tallman, Undated; cuid24210 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Asylum (Parts 2,5,6,7), glaucon55, 1998; cuid24211 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - At Their Mercy (Part 13), Dream Spinner, 1998; cuid24212 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Auto Serviced, Shaun Dayton, 2000, cuid24213 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - The B'anati (Part 1-6), Mickey (Daddy), 1999, cuid24214 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Back Wash Mountain Man, David L. Hass, 2000; cuid24215 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Bagging a Bagger, Unknown, Undated; cuid24216 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Bamacop, Cagecashier, 1997, cuid24217 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Barbershop Boy (Part 2), Randyboy, 1999, cuid24218 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Barn Boy, Dale10, 2000; cuid24219 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Baseball Player in the Rest Area; Biting Off a Homer; Proper Submission; Eating Straight Surfer Shit, Unknown, 1999; cuid24220 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Baseball Team Rapes Teacher, Conor O'Leary, 1999, cuid24221 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Bastille, Unknown, Undated; cuid24222 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Baxter and Joey, Badaug, 1997, cuid24223 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Bear Ass Quarterbackin' (Parts 1,2), Michael Dionne, 2001; cuid24224 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Bear Cop 2, Bearbtmboys, 2003, cuid24225 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Bear in the Woods, BlackBearLover, 1997, cuid24226 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Bear's Hairy Dick, Micfriend, Undated; cuid24227 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Becoming A Real Man (Part 1), Tom Borden, 2003; cuid24228 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Behind the Bar, Unknown, 1997; cuid24229 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Best Fag, Man Loving, 1996, cuid24230 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - The Best Stop, Eirewolf, 2000, cuid24231 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Big Brother's Bopper- V, Balsam8, 2000; cuid24232 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Big Hairy Boss, Story Teller, 2000, cuid24233 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Big Jake, Blackmansboy, 2000, cuid24234 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Big Luke, Nathan Harvey, 1999, cuid24235 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Big Sky Buddy, Sniff42, 1999, cuid24236 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Bill and Mike, and Carla; Cuckold and Loving It, Ooz, Undated; cuid24237 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - A BJ for the Plumber, Unknown, Undated; cuid24238 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Black & White Night, JonH, 2001, cuid24239 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Black Daddy's Slut, Michael, 2000, cuid24240 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Black Dominance, White Submission, Kevin James, 2000; cuid24241 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Black Man's White Pussyboy (Part 1- 2), Percxyz, 2001; cuid24242 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Black N White Night, Jon H, 2001, cuid24243 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Black Neighbour 3, Unknown, 2002; cuid24244 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Black Sperm Engines (Part 2), Braveheart_sm, 2000; cuid24245 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Black Stud in the Military, Mark Daniels, Undated; cuid24246 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Blackstud in the Morning, EbonyLover, 2000, cuid24247 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Blues Cock (Parts 1-3), Ron Kelly, 2002, cuid24248 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Bob Maloney's Boys, Xwriter, Undated; cuid24249 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Bonding with Coach, GoJackgo, 1998, cuid24250 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - The Book Seller, dale10, 2000; cuid24251 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Bookstore Lust 2, Grtbttm2, 2000; cuid24252 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - The Boss's New Sub, Rob D., 2000, cuid24253 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - The Boy Who Cried Wolf (Part 2), Happenstance, 1999; cuid24254 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - The Boyfriend: At Joey's House, Dale10, 1999; cuid24255 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Boys "Do" Men, BALSAM8, 1999; cuid24256 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - The Boys In the Band, Unknown, Undated; cuid24257 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Brawn, Mark, Undated; cuid24258 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Bringing Lenny Along, Roderick Shafton, 2001; cuid24259 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Broken Jock (Part 1- 5), Alan, 2001, cuid24260 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Brother Lust (Part 4), Rim4You, 2000; cuid24261 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Brother Raunch, Mark Kelly, 1998, cuid24262 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Brother's First Time, D, 2000, cuid24263 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Brown Hanky, Rim4you, 2000; cuid24264 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Builder, Andy McDonald, Undated; cuid24265 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Bull Daddies (Part 4), WorshipsMusclesChubs, 2001; cuid24266 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Bull Session, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24267 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Burglars! Burglars!, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24268 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Bus Rider, Water Closet Clark, Undated; cuid24269 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Bus Station Hijinks #3, Cgard43, 1999, cuid24270 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Business Trip Abroad, Paul Richarson, 2000, cuid24271 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Butch, Charlie Brown, and Snoopy 2, 1999; cuid24272 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Butt Feast, Marc, 2001, cuid24273 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Butt Sniffer (Part 3), Marc, 2002, cuid24274 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - The Call, Copper, 1999, cuid24275 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Camping Dad's (Part 2), Roderick Shafton, 2000; cuid24276 (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Camping with Uncle Bob, Get2it, 2000, cuid24277 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Car Wash Man, Nick, 2000, cuid24278 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Card Slave Buddies, Unknown, Undated; cuid24279 (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Careful What You Say In Jest!, Bbrunner4, 2000; cuid24280 (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Carlito's Table (Parts 1, 2), Raunchiboi69, 2002; cuid24281 (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Carpe Diem, Jon Logan, 1999, cuid24282 (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Caught by Dad, Daddy's Boy, Undated; cuid24283 (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Caught In A Rundown (Parts 1, 2), PeterAinLA, 2001; cuid24284 (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - The Cave (Part 1), Rimpigfl, 2000, cuid24285 (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Cell Sex, Dwolf5, 2000, cuid24286 (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Chance Encounter, Champ, 2000, cuid24287 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Cheating Lover, Bawdy Pen, 2003, cuid24288 (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - City Slave, Scatwoman, 1997, cuid24289 (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Cleanin' Up Daddy, Jerry & Eric, 2000, cuid24290 (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - The Climbing Hut, aled7, 2000, cuid24291 (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Coach, Chris Newman, Undated; cuid24292 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Coach, Matti, 2002; cuid24293 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Coach: A Gay Chainletter, MuscleBear, exPECtation, Unknown, 1995; cuid24294 (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Coach Madison, Daniel Townsend, 1998, cuid24295 (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Coach's Ass, Part 2, CDBOY, 1998, cuid24296 (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Cody, Scott Brenson, Undated; cuid24297 (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - College Boys During Spring Break, ScatStud, Undated; cuid24298 (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Construction Dad (Parts 1, 2), Russell, 2000, cuid24299 (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Construction Hole, RC Barber, 2002, cuid24300 (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Construction Ride Home, JD, 2002, cuid24301 (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - Construction Site Daddies; Afternoon Shower with Cousin Zack; In Bed with My Uncle; Caught By Uncle, Ruff Tuff UK; Mark K; Mark, Undated; cuid24302 (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - Construction Stud Foreman (Part 2), Jay Cee, 2001; cuid24303 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - The Construction Stud Foreman (Parts 1,2 4-6), Jay Cee, 2001; cuid24304 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - The Construction Worker's Son (Parts 2,3), Rimpigfl, 2002; cuid24305 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - The Convention, Manekel, 2001, cuid24306 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - Convention of a Lifetime, Cliff Simpson, 2000, cuid24307 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Cop, Greg Griggs, 1998, cuid24308 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Cop, Ripinstick, 1999, cuid24309 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Cop, Unknown, Undated; cuid24310 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Cop (Part 2), Unknown, 1993; cuid24311 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cop Cadet, Bill Drake, 1999, cuid24312 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Cop Encounter, Unknown, Undated; cuid24313 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Cop Sex, Sam Rad, 1988, cuid24314 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Copsucker, Uknown author, and Copsucker (Part II), Dick Hunter, 1998, 2001; cuid24315 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cottage Fantasy, Antoms, 2001, cuid24316 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Country Boy, Marc Tremaine, 1998, cuid24317 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Country Life, an143969, 1995, cuid24318 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Countrylife, Kevin Mackenzie, 1998, cuid24319 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Cowboy, Scott Benson, 1997, cuid24320 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - A Cowboy Story, Unknown, Undated; cuid24321 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Cruising For Piss (Parts 1,2), Ron Kelly, 2002; cuid24322 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Cum Contest, An22313, 1995; cuid24323 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Cum Slut, Cum Drinker, 1999, cuid24324 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Cumshots & Pisstreams: Confessions of a Teenage Toilet (Parts 1-3), Jay, 2002; cuid24325 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Cuntboy (Part 1), Maipenraikhap, 2002, cuid24326 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - A Cup of Joe, Backlash, 1999, cuid24327 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Curiosity (Chapters 1-3,6-7,1-15,19,20-22), Shaver Boy, 2000; cuid24328 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Custodial Help, David L. Hass, 2000, cuid24329 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - A Dad and His Boy: A Love Story, PIGBoy32, 2000; cuid24330 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Dad and Me First Pee, Fckmedad, 2002, cuid24331 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Dad and Me in the Cornfield, R.N.E., Undated; cuid24332 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Dad and Me on the Farm, Duu634, 1998; cuid24333 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Dad and the Coach, Joshua A. Laff, 1993, cuid24334 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Dad-Discovers-Me, Alexander Phaeton, 1999, cuid24335 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Dad Fucked him at the ADB, coolblue35, 2003; cuid24336 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Dad in the Shower (Parts 1-3), Thom, 1998, cuid24337 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Dad, Me and our Horse Farm, Victorianboy, 2002; cuid24338 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Dad Teaches Me, duu634, 1998; cuid24339 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Daddies in the Lockers, Man Loving, 1997, cuid24340 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Daddy Daddy (Part 6), CandyMan, 2001, cuid24341 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Daddy Punishes His Boys With Sex, kinky_uncut_daddy, 1998; cuid24342 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Daddy Stan (Part 1), Frank Ward, 2001, cuid24343 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Daddy's Cocksucker, PigBoy32, 2001; cuid24344 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Daddy's Good Little Boy, Rimpigfl, 2000, cuid24345 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Daddy's Home, Dade Bryant, 2000, cuid24346 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Daddy's Pickups (parts 1, 2), Roderick Shafton, 2000; cuid24347 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Dad's Buddy Rene, Nick, 2000, cuid24348 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Dad's Club (Part 2), Maipenraikhap, 2002, cuid24349 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Dad's Cock, Ron, 1999, cuid24350 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Dad's Cockslave, raman5436, 2003; cuid24351 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Dad's Condom, Dkscorpio, 1999, cuid24352 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Dad's Demonstation, Edward Bangor, 1997, cuid24353 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Dad's Dirty Little Boy (Part 1 - 3), RimPigfl, 2003, cuid24354 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Dad's Golden Boy (Parts 1, 2), RimPigfl, 2001, cuid24355 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Dad's Lust, RC, 1999, cuid24356 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Dad's Outhouse, Mark Thomas, 1999, cuid24357 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Dad's Piss Fag (Part 1-5), Unknown, Undated; cuid24358 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Dad's Piss Fag 1, 4, and 5, Unknown, Undated; cuid24359 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Dad's Pussy, Happenstance, 1998, cuid24360 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Dad's Randy 4 (Chapter 12-15), Tyler Thane, 2001; cuid24361 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Dad's Shit Slave (Part 1), Josh Carr, 1999, cuid24362 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Dad's Stink, Marc, 2001, cuid24363 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Dad's "Woodie", Balsam8, 1999, cuid24364 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Danny's School Humiliation, Maipenraikhap, 2002; cuid24365 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - The Dare!, T. Bears, 1996, cuid24366 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Dario 'n Dad (Part 2), D. B. Reed, 1997, cuid24367 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Dark Corners, Loopy, Undated; cuid24368 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Darn Hot, Pete Conway, Undated; cuid24369 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Dave's Bitch, Jay S, 2000, cuid24370 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - A Day at the Beach, Unknown, Undated; cuid24371 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - A Day in July, Paul and Don, Undated; cuid24372 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Denver, the Biker, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24373 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Depraved (Parts1- 3), Bawdy Pen, 2002, cuid24374 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Depraved Cravings, Toilet Mike, 2000, cuid24375 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Destroyed Mind, Devil Dog, 2000, cuid24376 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Deviant Lust, 12 Inch Jesus, 2001; cuid24377 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Diaper, Unknown, 1998; cuid24378 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Directions (Part 1), Pete, 2000; cuid24379 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Dirty Boy Next Door, AmuseBouche, Undated; cuid24380 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Dirty Little Altar Boys, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24381 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Dirtpig: A Weekend of Raunch, Unknown, 1993; cuid24382 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Dog Pound Daze, (Parts 4-6, 11), lennoxbear, 2000; cuid24383 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Dog Surprise, Varstin, 2000; cuid24384 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Dominated By Doug (Parts 4, 11-13), Perryxyz, 1999, cuid24385 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Domination of a Quarterback-04, Jonathan, 2000; cuid24386 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Doorbell, Anthony Thomas, 1999, cuid24387 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - The Doting Wife, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24388 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Doug Does The Gang 10, Chartoe, 2003, cuid24389 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Douglasville Dilemma, Sniff42, Undated; cuid24390 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Doug's Experience, Paul Haakonsen, 1998, cuid24391 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Down on the Docks, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24392 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Downstairs At The Fox... (Part 1-3), Willingmike, 2003, cuid24393 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Drew Gets Passed Around (Part 1), Brandon Richardson, 2002; cuid24394 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Drill Sergeant Gets Drilled (Parts 1, 2), Bill Drake, 2002; cuid24395 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Drunk Enough, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24396 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - The Dumping Ground, Scatboy, 2000, cuid24397 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Eatin' It At The Baths (Parts 1, 2), Bkcycler, 2001; cuid24398 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Eating Latino Dump: A True Story, RimGuy, 2001, cuid24399 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Eating Nevada Beef, Rimguy, Undated; cuid24400 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Eating Shit In Dr. Jack's Lab; A Night To Remember; Fly Catcher, Butch, Toilet Mike; Sxuldev8, 2000; cuid24401 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Engineered, V9irjim, 2000, cuid24402 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - The English Boy 24: 'Peter's Story', Philip Burbidge, 2000; cuid24403 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Enslaved, Dale10, 1999; cuid24404 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Enslaved Followup, Maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24405 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Eric, Hidden 12, 1996, cuid24406 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - An Evening with Gamal, Arablover, Undated; cuid24407 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - The Executive, Eryck, Undated; cuid24408 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - An Experiment with Manuel, loopy, 1998, cuid24409 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Family Business (Parts 5-6, 8-11), Jack Doegh, 2000; cuid24410 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Family Friction (Part 5), Rim4you, 2000; cuid24411 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Family Fuck (Parts 1-13), Roarr201, 1999; cuid24412 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fantasy Fulfilled at the Watersports Club, Wellington Club, Undated; cuid24413 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Fanta$y $eduction, Hair Lover, 1997, cuid24414 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Farmer Brown, Nathan Harvey, 1999, cuid24415 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Father, Unknown, Undated; cuid24416 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Father Takes Charge Pt. 3, Phill, 1999, cuid24417 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Father's Night (Parts 1-3), LCdrObrien, 1999, cuid24418 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Favor, Bawdypen, 2000, cuid24419 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Favor, Bbrunner4, 2000, cuid24420 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Feeding and Breeding Sean & Brendan (Part 2), Dick Hunter, 2001; cuid24421 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - A Few Good Men (Parts 2, 3), Billy Bob, 1999, cuid24422 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Field Manuvers, R. Keith Peck, 1996, cuid24423 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Finally, Used As The Slut I Am, Isuckall, Undated; cuid24424 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - First Time With Dad, Unknown, Undated; cuid24425 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Five the Hard Way, Wildstyle, 1998, cuid24426 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The Flange, Bushy Pits, 2000; cuid24427 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Flycatcher, Sxuldev8, 2000, cuid24428 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Foggy Night, Tjo1, Undated; cuid24429 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Folsom Street, Wolter, 1998, cuid24430 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Football Fuck, F.U.C.K, 1999, cuid24431 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Forced Dog Fuck, Beef Rian, 2000, cuid24432 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Force Fucked in the Forest, Rectufill, 2000, cuid24433 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Foreman, Myoder, 1996, cuid24434 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Forest Rain, Rene, 1998, cuid24435 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Fourth of July Faggot, and Fourth of July Too, Maipenraikhap, 2002; cuid24436 (Box 22, Folder 27)